Dilip Singh

fullStack webDeveloper

https://github.com/learnerdilip https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilip-singh-033a2a36/



SKILLS

TECHNOLOGY:

Javascript(ES6)

React / redux

NodeJS

HTML5

CSS3

Express

REST APIs

Postgres SQL

Sequelize

Bootstrap

Material UI

Git, Github

CLI

Docker

TypeScript

BUSINESS:

UX

UI Design

Wireframing

DigitalMarketing

GoogleAnalytics

FB Ads

Google Ads

User Research

CONTACT

dilip.singh@iiml.org 0633030215 Rotterdam

PROFILE

After working for more than 4 years solving Business challenges, now I completed accelerated boot-camp to switch career to align with my enthusiasm for technology. Now, my focus is to use that knowledge in making useful and high quality applications that help solve problems. I am looking for a role as web developer for a company that provides a mix of challenge and opportunity. I am a conceptual thinker with ability to break down a complex problem

WORK EXPERIENCE

Codaisseur - Full stack Developer Trainee

Invoice/Warranty manager - (FullStack - React, Express, Postgres, REST API, Docker, JWT) An online Warranty management App to keep your appliance Invoices/warranties safe and get custom notifications about their expiration (Github Link)

LabBook - (FullStack)

An online lab notebook to keep track of experiments progress in a scientific Lab with option to note ideas and a todo list

Ticket swapping platform - (FullStack)

An online platform where user can create account and create events, add tickets and comments

Times Internet - Project Manager

September 2015 - September 2018

- Defined user journey for OTT content App through GoogleAnalytics
- Improved conversion rate (purchase/visit) by 50% through improvements to design and better definition of customer journey

ICICI Bank - Wealth Manager

February 2015 - February 2017

Gathering financial requirements and coming up with asset allocation plan.
Generated highest revenue for 2 consecutive quarters for the bank in North Zone

Newgen Software - Business Analyst

December 2013 - February 2015

• Successfully identified business need through requirements gathering and helping generate additional revenue for the company and a useful feature for the client

EDUCATION

CODAISSEUR BOOTCAMP

Full-stack Web development course following AGILE Methodology (Jan 2020 - Mar 2020)

IIM LUCKNOW

Masters in Business Administration (June 2011 - Feb 2013)

PEC, CHANDIGARH

Bachelors in Computer Science Engineering (June 2006 - June 2010)